Guide to the Association for Union Democracy: Women's Project Records WAG 331
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Subject and Organization Files, 1974-2004, 1947-2004 (Bulk 1980-2002); 306952; 14 Linear Feet
  - United States of America v. New York City Police Department: Settlement Agreement, 1998; 308384 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of Labor, 1991-2001; 308385 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Labor: Equal Employment Opportunity, 1982-1989; 308386 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Labor: Publications, 1987-1999; 308387 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau, 1996-1998; 308388 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - "Directory of Non-Traditional Training and Employment Programs Serving Women", 1991; 308389 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - "Facts on Working Women", 1986-2000; 308390 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - Labor Secretary Elaine Chao, 1994-2001; 308391 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - United States Department of Labor:Women's Bureau - Printed Ephemera, c. 1991; 308392 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - Publications, 1980-1985; 308393 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - Publications, 1986-1998; 308394 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Unites States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - "Time of Change: 1983 Handbook on Women Workers", 308395 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - "Working Women Count! A Report To the Nation", 1994; 308405 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - United States Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1996-1997; 308406 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1991; 308407 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - United Tradeswomen, 1989-1990, 2001; 308408 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "United Tradeswomen: The Nuts and Bolts of Women's Grassroots Activism in the New York City Construction Industry, 1979-1984" (Masters Thesis), 2001; 308409 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - University of California, Berkeley: 3rd Annual Western Regional Summer Institute for Union Women, 1984; 308410 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - University and College Labor Education Association (UCLEA), 1992-2000; 308411 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Urban Justice Center: "Welfare, Workfare, and Jobs: An Educator's Guidebook", 1998; 308412 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Utility Workers of America, 1979-1990; 308413 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Wider Opportunities for Women, Inc.: Women's Work Force Network, 1989-1990; 308414 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Women Electricians, 1991-1992; 308415 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Women and Employment, Inc., 1985-1991; 308416 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Women Fighting Poverty Conference, 1997-2001; 308417 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Women and Foundations / Corporate Philanthropy, 1986; 308418 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - "Women In the American Welfare Trap", 1996; 308419 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Women in the Building Trades, 1989-1990; 308420 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Women in the Fire Service, Inc., 2000-2001; 308421 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Women in Non-Traditional Work, Inc.: Tradeswomen of Philadelphia, 1988-1991; 308422 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Women in the Public Sector, 1985-1992; 308423 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Women in the Trades, 1988-1993; 308424 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Women in the Trades Conference (I), 1990; 308425 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Women in the Trades Conference (II), 1992; 308426 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Women in the Trades Conference (III), 1992; 308427 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Women in the Trades Conference: Printed Ephemera, 1992; 308428 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Women in Trades Fair, 1991-1992; 308429 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Women in Trades, Technology, Operations & Blue Collar Work, 1992; 308434 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Women in Union Leadership, c. 1990-1994; 308435 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Women of the New York Fire Department: Stories and Struggles, Mar 2001; 308436 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Women Office Workers: Research and Education Project, Inc., 1981; 308437 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Women on the Job, 1986-1988; 308438 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Women on the Job, 1989; 308439 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Women on the Job, 1990-1993; 308440 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Women on the Job: Pay Equity, 1987-1990; 308441 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Women on the Job Task Force, 1995-2000; 308442 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "Women Union Electricians: A Comparison of Job and Training Experiences of White Women and Women of Color" (A Thesis), 1995; 308443 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Women, Work and Welfare, 1987-1988; 308444 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Women's Alliance for Job Equity (WAJE), 1990-1993; 308445 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Women's Caucus of the Democratic National Committee: "Gender Gap Issues and What You Need to Know about Them", 1992; 308446 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Women's Enews, 2001; 308447 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - The Women's Foundation, 1989-1990; 308448 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Women's Funds, 1990; 308449 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Women's History Month, 1990, 2001-2002; 308450 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Women's Institute for Leadership Development (WILD), 1989-1992; 308451 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Women's Legal Defense Fund, 1990; 308452 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Women's Organizations: Brochures, 1988-1991; 308453 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Women's Project of Little Rock, AR (Non-Affiliated), undated; 308454 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Words of Wit (Minnesota Women in the Trades), 1993-2000; 308455 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Working/Women's Institute, 1980-1983; 308456 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - World March of Women, 1998; 308457 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - YWCA of Brooklyn - Planned Parenthood: "Women of Influence", 1993; 308458 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - YWCA: Women in Trades Project, undated; 308459 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Photographs: Exhibits and Conferences, 1994, 1998 (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 3)